boltbus.com 2013-12-19

# BoltBus - Privacy Policy

As a valued consumer, you are entitled to your personal privacy. With that in mind, BoltBus has adopted a statement that explains and confirms our commitment to provide you with a variety of travel services while maintaining your personal privacy. Please note that this statement is subject to change at any time without notice. Every effort, however, will be made to keep it updated to reflect our current policies. 

Sharing of Personal Information

BoltBus will never sell your personal or financial information to any third party, but may be shared with our affiliates. Your personal or financial information, however, may be shared with third parties, who are authorized by BoltBus, for the following purposes: 

  * Credit card verification and fraud detection purposes as part of your ticket purchase;
  * Legal disclosure to a governmental agency, law enforcement authority or court as required by law in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary or advisable.

In addition, if you decide to participate in our marketing programs (including but not limited to Bolt Rewards, promotions or contests), your non-financial personal information may be released to reputable third parties in order to fulfill certain business requirements of those programs. 

Personal Information Collected For Processing Transactions

BoltBus collects personal information (name, address, phone number, etc.) as well as a credit card number to process transactions. An e-mail address for an online purchase is optional; however, your e-mail address is required if you would like a copy of your confirmation statement e-mailed to you. 

For Marketing Programs

By participating in our marketing programs, you agree to honor and abide by the rules and regulations contained therein. Please read all rules before participating. BoltBus takes no responsibility for the specific privacy rules or terms and conditions of the contest sponsors or other third parties and we encourage you to examine the privacy policies contained on these sites. 

Online Collection of Personal Information

BoltBus's website is not directed at children under the age of thirteen, and accordingly, BoltBus does not intentionally collect any personal information from anyone under age thirteen. 

Non-Personal Information Collected

IP Addresses

An Internet protocol ("IP") address is a numeric code, for example, "152.163.207.197." This code is used to communicate between your Internet service provider and the World Wide Web. The IP address does not identify you individually. BoltBus logs inbound IP addresses to administer our Web site and to compile aggregate information on site traffic for internal use. 

Cookies

Cookies (and similar files such as single pixel GIF's, web beacons or tags) are small computer files written to your computer when you visit Web sites. You have the option of setting your browser to refuse cookies. To utilize all promotional offers and discounts on Bolt.com you need to allow temporary "session cookies" that will go away when your browser is closed. No personal or credit card information is collected by any Bolt related cookies.

BoltBus cookies collect anonymous, non-personal information to make your use of the web site easier and allow BoltBus to track and improve the effectiveness of our on-line advertising. For example, when you check the appropriate box a Bolt cookie will remember your origination and destination locations.

Opt-Out Policy

You have the option of being excluded from the various marketing contact lists by opting out at any time. Opt-out requests for contests, however, must be received within the duration of the contest to be removed for that contest. To stop messages coming to your cell phone, just reply "STOP." To opt out, update or change any contact information send us an e-mail to [webmaster@boltbus.com](mailto:webmaster@boltbus.com&subject=Further%20Opt%20Out) with your name, e-mail address and mailing address.

Security

BoltBus takes reasonable procedures to protect your personal and credit card information from misuse or unauthorized disclosure. For example, BoltBus uses encryption software from VeriSign, the industry leader in secure site software technologies to protect your information. 

Look for the gold key (Internet Explorer) or lock (Netscape) as well as the "s" after "http" in the address line of your browser. These signs mean the information sent from your computer to Boltbus.com is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

Links to Other Websites

While we strive to partner with reputable firms, BoltBus takes no responsibility for any content, information collected, terms and conditions or privacy rules maintained on any linked site and we strongly encourage you to examine the privacy policies contained on these sites. Please inform us at [webmaster@boltbus.com](mailto:webmaster@boltbus.com&subject=Further%20Linked%20Sites) about any concerns you may have regarding any of our linked sites. 

Consent

Your use of BoltBus's Web site, services and participation in our marketing programs is your express consent to BoltBus to use your personal information as described above. We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy from time to time, without prior notice, and for this reason, we encourage you to review the policy posted at www.boltbus.com periodically. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions about the use of your personal information or would like to correct or amend any personal information we maintain about you, please feel to contact us at [webmaster@boltbus.com](mailto:webmaster@boltbus.com&subject=Further%20Questions), or send a letter to: 

BoltBus  
IT Webmaster/MS850  
P.O. Box 660362  
Dallas, TX 75266-0362

Revised March 1, 2008
